miniup.net 2009-08-30

# Miniup.Net Free File Hosting - Easy way to share your files

Do you know what Forex trading is? Some people have heard of this type of trading, others have not. If you haven't, it might be something you are interested in trying. Forex trading stands for foreign exchange trading. What it consists of is the buying and selling of different currencies. This is done simultaneously, and there are people who make a lot of money with this kind of trading. This is apparent by the 1.9 million dollar turnover in this market that happens every day. Also a lot of it is done online. Online Forex trading is very popular.

Online Forex trading sites are easy to find by surfing the Internet. Most of them provide a wealth of information for the first time trader. You can find out about the history of Forex trading, how to co it, tips on being successful, etc. You can also start trading with as little as $250 in your account on some sites. For anyone who is interested in currency or trading, it is something you should check out.

## Privacy policy

#### Commitment

Miniup.Net provider of online storage and web hosting services offering free and affordable premium online storage capacity. This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of Miniup.Net's policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any Personal Information you submit to us through our website.

Miniup.Net ("us" or "we") respects the privacy of the visitors to its website. Miniup.Net may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes by placing a prominent notice on this page and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

#### Registering IP addresses

For each visitor, our web server does not recognize any information regarding the domain or e-mail address. IP addresses are logged and used identify our visitors.

#### Collecting e-mail addresses

Our service collects email addresses belonging to senders and receivers for the purpose of logging and measuring usage. Miniup.Net does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated companies.

#### Certain exceptional disclosures

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct or potential threats to the physical safety of any person. The disclosure of personal information may be required by court or law enforcement officials.

#### Using cookies

Miniup.Net uses cookies to store the preferences and tracking trends of users. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie.

#### File transfer security

We accept all the possible security measures on our servers in order to prevent the loss of data, inaccurate use of information, as well as file damage. Files saved for transferring are available for viewing only to Miniup.Net representatives or via the link that is given to the user who uploaded the file. Files saved on our server are deleted automatically after a certain period of time.

#### Credit card security

All purchases on Miniup.Net are handled by a third party payment systems: PayPal.com, Plimus.com, SegPay.com. Miniup.Net does not arrange and/or save numbers or any information from your credit cards.

#### Advertising through intermediaries

Ads on our website are presented by advertising intermediaries. These companies may use information concerning your visiting our website and other web pages (excluding your personal info, such as name, address, email address and phone number) with the purpose of advertising products and services that would interest you most as a perspective customer.

#### Third party cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

#### External links

If any part of the Miniup.Net website links you to other websites, those websites do not operate under this Privacy Policy. We recommend you examine the privacy statements posted on those other websites to understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing personal information.

#### Contact information

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
